<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="game.controller.arcade.neogeo"
        name="Neo Geo Controller"
        version="1.0.23"
        provider-name="Team Kodi">
    <extension point="kodi.game.controller" library="resources/layout.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
        <summary lang="da_DK">Neo Geo controller</summary>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Neo Geo Controller</summary>
        <summary lang="it_IT">Controller Neo Geo</summary>
        <summary lang="ru_RU">Контроллер Neo Geo</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_CN">Neo Geo 控制器</summary>
        <description lang="da_DK">Controlleren til Neo Geo AES (Advanced Entertainment System); en videospilkonsol, der blev udgivet i USA i 1991. Neo Geo AES var et nichesystem, der blev markedsført mod avancerede forbrugere. Konsollen var dyr, ligesom selve spilene, som kunne sælges for hundreder af dollars.</description>
        <description lang="en_GB">The controller for the Neo Geo AES (Advanced Entertainment System), a video game console released in the US in 1991. The Neo Geo AES was a niche system marketed toward high-end consumers. The console was expensive, as were the games themselves, which could go for hundreds of dollars.</description>
        <description lang="it_IT">Il controller per Neo Geo AES (Advanced Entertainment System), una console per videogiochi rilasciata negli Stati Uniti nel 1991. Il Neo Geo AES era un sistema di nicchia commercializzato per i consumatori di fascia alta. La console era costosa, così come i giochi stessi, che potevano arrivare a centinaia di dollari.</description>
        <description lang="ru_RU">Контроллер для Neo Geo AES (Advanced Entertainment System), игровой консоли, выпущенной в США в 1991 году. Neo Geo AES была нишевой системой, предназначенной для элитных потребителей. Консоль была дорогой, как и сами игры, которые могли стоить сотни долларов.</description>
        <description lang="zh_CN">Neo Geo AES（Advanced Entertainment System 高级娱乐系统）控制器，1991年在美国发布的一款视频游戏机。Neo Geo AES 是面向高端消费者的定制系统。游戏机很贵，游戏也很贵，要几百美元。</description>
    </extension>
</addon>
