<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<addon id="game.controller.vb"
        name="Nintendo Virtual Boy Controller"
        version="1.0.30"
        provider-name="Team Kodi">
    <extension point="kodi.game.controller" library="resources/layout.xml"/>
    <extension point="xbmc.addon.metadata">
        <platform>all</platform>
        <assets>
            <icon>resources/icon.png</icon>
        </assets>
        <summary lang="da_DK">Nintendo Virtual Boy controller</summary>
        <summary lang="de_DE">Nintendo Virtual Boy Controller</summary>
        <summary lang="en_GB">Nintendo Virtual Boy controller</summary>
        <summary lang="es_ES">Mando Nintendo Virtual Boy</summary>
        <summary lang="fi_FI">Nintendo Virtual Boy -ohjain</summary>
        <summary lang="fr_FR">Manette Nintendo Virtual Boy</summary>
        <summary lang="it_IT">Controller Nintendo Virtual Boy</summary>
        <summary lang="zh_CN">任天堂 Virtual Boy 控制器</summary>
        <description lang="da_DK">The Virtual Boy er en 32-bit konsol udgivet af Nintendo i 1995. Mens Nintendo lovede en virtual reality-oplevelse, førte det røde monokrome display og det store bordmonterede headset til en dårlig fordybende oplevelse.</description>
        <description lang="de_DE">Der Virtual Boy ist eine 32-Bit-Konsole, die 1995 von Nintendo veröffentlicht wurde. Nintendo versprach zwar ein Virtual-Reality-Erlebnis, doch das rote Monochrom-Display und das sperrige, auf dem Tisch montierte Headset sorgten für ein wenig realistisches Erlebnis.</description>
        <description lang="en_GB">The Virtual Boy is a 32-bit console released by Nintendo in 1995. While Nintendo promised a virtual reality experience, the red monochrome display and bulky table-mounted headset lead to a poor immersive experience.</description>
        <description lang="es_ES">La Virtual Boy es una videoconsola de 32 bits lanzada por Nintendo en 1995. Aunque Nintendo prometió una experiencia de realidad virtual, la pantalla monocromática roja y el voluminoso casco con pantalla en la cabeza dan lugar a una experiencia de inmersión deficiente.</description>
        <description lang="fi_FI">Virtual Boy on 32-bittinen konsoli, jonka Nintendo julkaisi vuonna 1995. Vaikka Nintendo lupasi virtuaalitodellisuuskokemuksen, yhden punaisen värin näyttö ja isot pöytään kiinnitetyt kuulokkeet eivät tarjonneet immersiivistä kokemusta.</description>
        <description lang="fr_FR">La Virtual Boy est une console 32 bits lancée par Nintendo en 1995. Alors que Nintendo promettait une expérience de réalité virtuelle, l&apos;écran monochrome rouge et le casque volumineux conduisent à une mauvaise expérience immersive.</description>
        <description lang="it_IT">The Virtual Boy è una console a 32 bit rilasciata da Nintendo nel 1995. Mentre Nintendo ha promesso un&apos;esperienza di realtà virtuale, il display monocromatico rosso e le ingombranti cuffie da tavolo portano a un&apos;esperienza scarsamente coinvolgente.</description>
        <description lang="zh_CN">Virtual Boy 是任天堂在1995年发布的一款32位游戏机。尽管任天堂承诺提供虚拟现实体验，但红色单色显示屏和笨重的桌上耳机导致了糟糕的沉浸体验。</description>
        <disclaimer lang="da_DK">Kildeangivelse: OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="de_DE">Bildverweis: OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="en_GB">Image credit: OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es_ES">Créditos de la imagen: OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="es_MX">Créditos de la imagen: OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="eu_ES">Irudiaren kreditua: OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fi_FI">Kuvan lähde: OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="fr_FR">Crédit image : OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="it_IT">Credito immagine: OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="nl_NL">Bron afbeelding: OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="ru_RU">Источник изображения: OpenEmu (openemu.org)</disclaimer>
        <disclaimer lang="zh_CN">图片来源：OpenEmu（openemu.org）</disclaimer>
    </extension>
</addon>
